[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[panting]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[grunts, panting]
[exhales, panting]
[continues panting] Oh, oh...
[Isoo continues panting]
Kid, go inside.
Go inside!
[exhales anxiously]
Your heart's pounding.
[kid breathing shakily]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Drop the knife.
There's nowhere left to run.
Should I kill him?
[Pilgu] Drop it.
I'll slice his neck.
[Hyera] Fine.
Calm down.
[Pilgu] Put it down.
Get back.
Drop it.
Drop it, you bastards!
[kid panting frantically]
I said, drop it, you bastards!
[taser fires, crackling]
[grunting, convulsing]
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
[mimics gunshot] You're no big deal.
[grunting]
[siren blaring]
[Taegyun] What's going on?
What's the case?
EPISODE 12
This is the real killer
who set Detective Jin up.
What are you talking about?
Sir! It's been a while.
Wait, he's...
Detective Jin, when did you get out?
Yesterday.
I was kind of hurt.
What was it you said to me?
[mimicking Taegyun]
"A goddamn detective killed someone?"
How could you say that to me?
I liked you, sir, but you've let me down.
[Isoo swears softly]
[huffs] Let's go.
[Taegyun] Hey...
He won't try to get back at me, will he?
Oh, this is bad, sir.
He doesn't really let things go.
I think he'll try to get revenge.
This could get really ugly.
Goodness.
- Honestly, that punk.
- [♪ music fades]
You did this, didn't you?
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
Kim Younghwan drugged me unconscious...
then let you inside.
What were you two trying to do?
Why did you kill Younghwan?
We found a bag containing
50 million won inside your house.
FORENSIC INVESTIGATION
POLICE
[camera shutter clicking]
Where did you get it?
[yawns]
We found your car, too.
You took the subway from the scene,
then got into your car
at a public parking lot.
[camera shutter clicking]
[♪ music swells, fades]
We're investigating it right now.
We'll find evidence soon.
Just come clean.
[clears throat]
I want to call my lawyer.
I want my phone call.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[cell phone vibrating]
[cell phone continues vibrating]
[exhales softly]
Mr. Lawyer.
I've been caught.
You're not very skilled.
Of course, I know you well, Mr. Lawyer.
I know exactly who you are.
You know me?
You're famous.
I'm more thorough than you think.
Then why did you get caught?
Uh...
I was unlucky.
In any case,
you'll have to come down here.
I'll send you a lawyer,
so don't say anything.
[whispering] You'd better hurry.
I'm...
not very patient.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
GRUDGE, ACCOMPLICE?
HOLDS DEEP GRUDGE AGAINST JIN ISOO
FOUR STABS TO CHEST, ABDOMEN, BACK
Did you find anything?
There's nothing at the house
but the cash bag.
Blood was found on the steering wheel.
They're checking it
against Kim Younghwan's DNA.
That's not enough.
You stabbed Kim Younghwan
and he went in there to save him.
That makes sense, too.
Isn't there a way to make him confess?
He said he won't talk without a lawyer.
[scoffs softly] With four convictions,
he knows how this works.
But I can't see the bigger picture.
Someone gave him that money to do this.
Who could it be?
Maybe he was called in to kill you,
then things went wrong.
No, that's not what Younghwan said.
What would happen
if the great Jin Isoo ended up in prison?
He wanted you to get arrested for murder?
Like that case where he was the suspect?
Mmm?
He was the initial suspect
in the murder of actress Han Yura.
He fell asleep after taking drugs,
and there was blood on his clothes.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Then,
he ordered Cho Pilgu to kill him?
To send Isoo to prison?
I don't think anyone would go that far.
KIM YOUNGHWAN, CHO PILGU
ACCOMPLICE?
For now, let's look into Cho Pilgu.
See if there's a way to make him confess.
Did you bring back Cho Pilgu's computer?
Yes, Forensics is going through it.
[♪ music swells, fades]
[sighs deeply]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
YU SEONGWON
STUDIO
[♪ music increases in tempo]
YU SEONGWON
[♪ music fades]
[door closes]
Are you two sleeping together?
Don't you know how to knock?
I wasn't really brought up properly.
At least I got a good show.
What do you want?
For you to be a mother for once.
Actually,
this is more important for you in the end.
You know Hansu Group's
Jin Isoo got arrested, right?
He was released yesterday.
That was my doing.
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[sighs softly]
4 WEEKS BEFORE KIM YOUNGHWAN'S DEATH
Thank you for your time.
[Seongwon] Of course. Thank you.
[chuckles softly]
[clears throat]
[Younghwan] Hey, Seongwon.
Congratulations.
Hey, I'm hurt.
It's me, Younghwan. Isoo's friend.
We met a couple of times before.
Ah.
Right.
- Here.
- Uh, thank you.
[chuckles softly]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Isoo was here yesterday.
Uh... Really?
[chuckles softly] Hey...
Anyway, I'm impressed.
You've become such a famous artist.
Even I'm proud of you.
[chuckles softly]
How did you make all these amazing pieces?
[chuckles]
[inhales sharply]
Anyway, the thing is,
there's something I want to discuss.
Can I visit you at your studio sometime?
Of course. Feel free to come.
Okay.
I'll call you soon.
Congratulations again.
[♪ ominous, ticking music playing]
[scoffs softly]
He's like a dog without its master.
[♪ music swells, fades]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[exhales contentedly]
[exhales] Even the whiskey you drink
is good.
This is the one Isoo made.
Never tried it before?
Uh... [chuckles nervously]
No. [scoffs]
[scoffs softly]
Anyway... [sighs]
...shouldn't you start thinking about
selling your pieces now?
Mmm.
The thing is,
I'm well-connected with
chaebols, celebrities, and big spenders.
People are already lining up
to buy your work.
Really?
You have no idea.
Right now, they keep calling me
to ask if they can buy your work.
[chuckling]
So, how about it?
Should I take this chance
and become your art dealer?
Uh, don't get me wrong. [chuckles]
I'm not trying to use this
to make money or anything like that.
Your work is just too good.
You run a production company.
[chuckles nervously]
Yeah, well,
I'm thinking of quitting.
So the rumors were true.
Mmm?
I heard you went to prison
for doing drugs.
- [sighs wearily]
- Why didn't Isoo help you back then?
Is that why you two fell out?
No.
That bastard turned me in.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
Uh...
Isoo did that?
Yeah. He was supposed to be my friend.
Uh...
But why?
He thinks he's a detective now. [scoffs]
Isoo thinks of himself as a detective?
That's why he sold out his own friend.
Are you just going to take that?
Actually, I was so pissed off,
I snuck into his house
and thought about killing him.
You snuck in?
I have a key to his house.
How about we mess with Isoo a little?
How?
[♪ music turns ominous]
Let's get him locked up for drugs, too.
You go inside
and make him take drugs somehow,
then I'll send someone.
He'll put Isoo in a car
and make him cause an accident.
I think it could become a huge scandal.
[laughs maliciously]
It's going to be so much fun.
[chuckles nervously]
Uh...
Aren't you close with Isoo?
Why would you do that?
He kind of screwed me over.
It's fine. It's just a joke.
Isoo will be able to get out of it anyway.
And you can just move abroad,
as my art dealer.
[chuckles nervously]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Find someone.
I need a job done.
Understood.
Are you saying
you gave the order to kill him?
- Yes.
- Why?
[♪ music fades]
Just because. I thought it'd be fun.
[scoffs]
[breathes deeply]
But
I think he found out who I am.
[♪ tense music playing]
How? You said Mr. Hwang hired him.
Yeah.
Mr. Hwang dropped off the money.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[keypad beeping]
He must've followed him.
[♪ music turns ominous]
You...
Why do you...
keep doing this?
It's a bit too late to ask that.
You should've asked when I was nine,
before you had me committed.
You might...
want to hurry.
If he decides to talk,
me,
you,
and this company you love so much
will be over.
[door opens]
[door slams]
[clink]
[screams in frustration]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs in exasperation]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
I'm Mr. Cho Pilgu's lawyer.
Okay.
[sighs in exasperation]
Song Yeonwoo.
First, please tell me what happened.
[breathes deeply]
There's nothing much to tell.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
He opened the door for me, so I went in.
You'll handle the rest, right?
I'll leave you to it.
[chuckles]
Wait.
What?
That's not what I was told.
What do you mean?
- [squelch]
- [Younghwan grunts softly]
- [groans]
- [squelch]
- [exclaims]
- [groaning]
- [squelching]
[exclaims]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
Come here.
- [squelch]
- [groans]
[exhales softly]
[knife clatters]
[Pilgu grunts]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[grunts]
[panting]
[♪ music swells]
[grunts]
[grunts] He's even heavier.
[♪ music resumes tempo]
Any fingerprints?
I was wearing gloves the whole time.
We can build a story.
The police don't have
any conclusive evidence.
We'll say Kim Younghwan took you there
as his bodyguard.
He was afraid Jin Isoo would kill him.
You went up there
because he called you for help.
That's how you got blood on you.
We might be here a while.
Why don't we eat something?
[chuckles softly]
- Sounds good.
- [♪ music fades]
[slurps]
Just stick to what we rehearsed.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
And sign this.
It's a retainer agreement.
[sighs deeply]
Such a hassle.
[slurps]
Expensive lawyers
are worth it.
Of course.
[chuckles smugly]
[slurping]
Eat up.
INTERVIEW ROOM
[♪ music fades]
They probably worked out a story.
Without more evidence,
we need to set Cho Pilgu free.
[sighs heavily]
Did you find anything?
His computer records came back,
but there was nothing significant.
Nothing on his phone either.
Let me see.
DIGITAL FORENSIC REPORT
YU SEONGWON
What's this?
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
He searched for Yu Seongwon online.
[Isoo] It's Yu Seongwon's studio.
Minjae installed another camera. Let's go.
Okay.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Look up Yu Seongwon.
Okay.
Did you hear anything about this?
No, nothing.
[line ringing]
[automated voice]
The number you have dialed...
- [line disconnects]
- He's not picking up.
[♪ music swells]
[sighs softly]
- [cell phone vibrates]
- [♪ music fades]
PI JEONG MINJAE
[Minjae] I can't pick up right now.
What is it?
[Hyera] Did anything happen
with Yu Seongwon yesterday?
[Minjae] He just went back to his studio.
[Hyera] Where are you?
[Minjae] I'm staking out
for a different case.
[breathes deeply]
Does Yu Seongwon know Kim Younghwan?
Yeah.
He met him a few times with me.
But why?
I get why Younghwan
would want to get back at me,
but what does Seongwon
have to do with this?
[♪ music swells, fades]
Do you know the passcode?
Yeah, we know each other's,
just to be safe.
[digital beeping]
[sighs softly]
That's the monitor for Yu Seongwon.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
- Let's check the saved files first.
- Okay.
[mouse clicking]
[Isoo] Oh.
That's Kim Younghwan.
[doorbell chiming]
Did they plan this together?
Yu Seongwon might have
wanted revenge on you.
He knows now that you suspect him.
He tried to frame me for murder
because of that?
Does that mean
Younghwan told Seongwon to murder him?
No, Kim Younghwan was
probably used as well.
Cho Pilgu went to Yu Seongwon's studio,
so Yu Seongwon must have hired him.
The 50 million won was
payment for the murder.
[♪ music fades]
Kim Younghwan's plan was something else,
but Yu Seongwon hired someone
to kill Kim Younghwan?
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
[Seongwon] I had a feeling
this day would come.
From the first day I met you.
Think back carefully.
Remember how good it felt
when you stabbed Younghwan.
[bang]
Don't run away from this.
Once you accept it,
you'll finally be free.
After all, you're my Little Prince.
It was to awaken me.
Yu Seongwon thinks I'm just like him.
That I'm
suppressing the urge to kill.
So he wanted to turn me
into a murderer like him.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[scoffs]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[grunts, groans]
[keyboard clacking]
[grunting, coughs]
Son of a...
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[keys jingling]
[latch clanks]
- [touch-tones beeping]
- [guard] A detainee collapsed.
Please call an ambulance.
[grunts, choking]
Cho Pilgu collapsed!
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
- [siren blaring]
- [camera shutters clicking]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
What happened?
It's an acute drug overdose.
That lawyer who came earlier.
I'm Mr. Cho Pilgu's lawyer.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[tires screech]
[♪ music swells]
ATTORNEY SONG YEONWOO
[♪ music resumes tempo]
How can I help you?
Are you Attorney Song Yeonwoo?
Yes, I'm Song Yeonwoo.
[sighs heavily]
[sighs softly]
[Junyoung sighs heavily]
He's been dealt with.
They won't find out who I am,
but I'll lie low for now.
You should delete me
from the company's records.
Well done.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[breathes deeply]
[sighs softly]
[Byungsik sighs wearily]
This doesn't look good.
How did this happen?
A suspect dying in police custody?
It looks like someone impersonated
a lawyer and drugged him.
Who? Did you find out who it was?
- No, not yet.
- Hey!
Are you trying to ruin me?
You idiots!
After all your fooling around,
this is what you come back with?
Who's going to answer for this?
Tell me, who?
- We'll make sure--
- Hey! You're seriously...
You.
You caused all of this.
Try to say another word.
I'll fire you on the spot!
Goddamn it!
[grunts angrily]
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
[sighs softly]
The incident at Detective Jin Isoo's--
Is it true that the suspect
of this case has died?
Yes, it's true.
How did they die in police custody?
We're still investigating that matter.
Is it true that the killer impersonated
a lawyer and poisoned him?
[reporters clamoring]
[♪ music swells]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[♪ music fades]
[exhales heavily]
I'm starving. Let's get something to eat.
Let's eat, then think about
how we'll catch Yu Seongwon.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
This might be an opportunity.
If we can prove
Yu Seongwon orchestrated the murder,
we can catch him
before he kills anyone else.
Yu Seongwon went to UBS's main office.
Minjae was following him
the day before Cho Pilgu died.
Maybe he met Jeong Taeseon that day
and asked for her help.
And Jeong Taeseon pulled something?
Yes.
[inhales sharply] There wasn't much time,
so it could be someone close to her.
[sighs heavily]
[line connects, ringing]
[automated voice]
The number you have dialed...
[sighs in exasperation]
Why won't he answer his phone?
[line disconnects]
[♪ music swells]
[sighs heavily]
[♪ music fades]
Ms. Joo Hyera?
Yes?
[delivery agent]
We have a delivery for you.
[delivery agents grunting]
[delivery agent dusts hands]
GANGHA POLICE STATION
DETECTIVE JOO HYERA
[door opens]
- What's that?
- Pass me a box cutter.
[door closes]
- [box cutter clicking]
- [tape slicing, ripping]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[♪ suspenseful sting plays]
[gasps softly]
[Hyera exhales in disbelief]
[whimpers]
[breath trembling]
Stop those delivery guys.
Got it.
[gasps, sobbing]
[♪ music swells]
Min...
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
[♪ music swells, fades]
There was a body inside?
We really don't know anything.
Where did you get it from?
[stutters] Namgye-dong.
But that place is a redevelopment area,
so everything's been cleared out.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
We were asked to move
something they left behind.
They said the money was on top of the box.
[gasps] Jesus Christ.
So you don't know
who commissioned the job?
We did get a call,
but when I tried the number just now,
the phone was off.
You don't know their name?
No.
We didn't catch the name.
You transported something
without knowing who hired you?
We've barely had any work recently.
And two million won is a lot of money.
[sighs softly]
[breathing heavily] You damn fool!
What the hell happened?
How did we get a body delivered?
You're all out of your damn minds!
Joo Hyera. Where the hell is Joo Hyera?
Let go of me!
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
[Taegyun panting softly]
Sir. [sighs softly]
For now,
please just stay put.
What?
The person who died
was Joo Hyera's junior officer.
He used to work for me, too.
[sighs softly]
I'll face disciplinary action,
or even resign if I have to,
so for now,
please don't say anything.
Please.
[Taegyun sighs softly]
[sniffles, crying]
[sighs deeply]
[gasps softly, breath trembling]
[exhales heavily]
[Changun] So it was Minjae.
Was Minjae the one
keeping an eye on Yu Seongwon?
[voice shaking] Minjae was
following Yu Seongwon.
I lost contact with him after that.
I didn't think anything of it.
[breath trembling]
[crying] I just waited.
[gasps softly, breath trembling]
[sighs deeply]
[sniffles]
[voice shaking] Did they find anything?
Not yet.
Let's give it some time.
If we search thoroughly,
I'm sure we'll find something.
No.
We won't find anything.
You know.
You know what Yu Seongwon is like.
Hyera.
Hey, Joo Hyera.
[♪ music fades]
Did you find anything of note?
[KCSI officer] Nothing in particular.
We'll go upstairs and check.
[engine accelerating]
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[Isoo] How did it go?
The truck doesn't seem related.
Forensics didn't find anything.
[sighs in exasperation]
How on earth did this happen?
And who's the person who died?
His name is Jeong Minjae.
Detective Joo's old colleague.
What?
What colleague...
You mean he's a police officer?
Not anymore.
They picked up the box from here,
so go with Forensics to check it out.
Okay.
Where's Detective Joo?
She left in a hurry earlier.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[engine accelerating]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
- [loud, distant bang]
- [alarm blaring]
[gate whirring]
[engine revs]
We have a guest.
Go and see.
[♪ foreboding, pulsating music playing]
Yu Seongwon is inside, isn't he?
Detective Joo Hyera.
Long time no see.
Why did you kill him?
What?
Hey!
Let go.
Leave. She's my guest.
I'm so sorry. He doesn't have any manners.
[chuckles]
Anyway,
did someone die?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
You think you're perfect, don't you?
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
You think after killing five people,
you didn't leave
a single trace, don't you?
[scoffs]
But you left a long trail this time.
You moved the body,
called a truck,
and sent it to me.
Why did you go that far?
Am I starting to scare you?
Are you finally afraid
you might get caught?
[scoffs]
Unbelievable.
[Seongwon] Everyone
asks me why.
"Why? Why on earth?"
As if they could understand
if I told them.
But the thing is,
there is no answer to begin with.
I am...
beyond the understanding
of someone like you.
You're right.
I treated you like a person,
when you're not even human.
I'm working on a new piece.
Would you like to see?
[♪ ominous sting plays]
[breath trembling]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gentle, poignant music playing]
Hey, I told you to stop coming.
I wouldn't have to come
if you had a girlfriend.
You didn't like the hospital food.
Oh, I can't resist fried chicken.
[chuckles softly]
[chuckles]
Here.
Hey, I told you
not to look at me like that.
What do you mean? Like what?
It was my mistake that got me stabbed,
so stop doing that.
[inhales deeply]
Your mistake is my mistake, too.
Seriously!
Fine, I'll stop.
Just eat up.
[chuckles]
- Is it good?
- [both chuckle]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[breath trembling]
[breathing shakily]
Are you that touched?
[grunts]
[Isoo] Detective Joo!
[Hyera crying]
Jeez. Isoo!
She's out of control right now.
[Hyera panting, breath trembling]
Are you going to trust someone like her?
You shut your mouth.
[scoffs, mutters]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ music fades]
It's possible he was murdered here.
- We need to find traces of blood.
- [KCSI officers] Okay.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
[♪ music fades]
[line connects, ringing]
[♪ somber, melancholy music playing]
[sighs softly]
- [sighs wearily]
- [cell phone vibrating]
Yeah. Did you find anything?
[Junyoung] No. [sighs]
There's no trace of blood anywhere.
This might not be where he was killed.
[cell phone snaps shut]
[line connects, ringing]
- [line clicks]
- Yes, Dr. Yoon.
Did you look at the body?
It looks like they used a stun gun.
There's an indentation
in the back of his head,
and there are bruises all over his body.
[sighs deeply]
[exhales softly]
Should I go in alone?
[exhales]
No, let's go together.
[♪ music fades]
At 11:00 p.m. on Sunday,
you went to UBS's main office.
Why?
Tell us what you did after that.
[sighs in exasperation]
This is seriously no fun. [clicks tongue]
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
[breathes deeply]
Isoo.
What are you doing?
Why do you keep pretending you're normal?
Are you going to
keep asking dumb questions?
How long do I have to keep
opening your eyes?
Right.
That's why you killed Younghwan.
Because you thought we were alike.
You said you grew up lonely.
That you felt abandoned.
You assumed we were the same
and got the wrong idea.
I'm not like you.
I had...
a mother who cherished me.
[♪ music turns ominous]
You didn't have a mother like that.
That's why you ended up completely broken.
You were damaged beyond repair.
After Kim Younghwan died
and Cho Pilgu was caught,
did you feel scared and run to your mom?
Did you beg her for help?
From the mom who despises you?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[scoffs softly]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
Hey, isn't that Chairwoman Jeong Taeseon?
I think it is.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
We're looking for the man
who impersonated a lawyer.
We're also combing through the place
where you disposed of the body.
We'll pull footage
from every camera nearby.
[♪ gripping, ominous music playing]
[sighs deeply]
I'm going to catch you in the end.
Save yourself the humiliation
of being dragged in and just confess.
[sighs, scoffs]
[laughing smugly]
Why do you keep saying I killed someone?
Why would I kill him?
I mean,
did he follow me...
and spy on me or something?
Because of his foolish superior
who thinks I'm a murderer?
Unless that's what pissed me off,
there's no reason for me to kill him.
Oh.
Right there.
That's a great expression.
Want to be my model?
[exhales sharply]
[♪ music fades]
Mr. Yu Seongwon, please get up.
[Seongwon sighs contentedly]
- Sir.
- Be quiet.
[scoffs softly]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[door closes]
[Hyera] Wait!
[Hyera panting]
Your son is a murderer.
He killed five people.
You know, don't you?
You're his mother.
Of course, you know.
He's going to continue killing people.
This isn't something you can cover up.
You have no manners.
And have no fear.
People like that
usually come to a bad end.
You should be careful.
[car door closes]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
Keep your subordinates in line!
Yes, sir.
For Christ's sake.
From now on,
this case goes to Team 2!
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
- You can't.
- I can't?
- I've been too patient with you.
- Sir.
[scoffs softly]
I heard the victim was
your junior officer.
Huh?
Can an involved party
be in charge of a case?
I'm the one
who knows this case best.
Yu Seongwon is the killer.
Do you have evidence?
I'm going to find it.
[scoffs] Isn't it all just in your head?
You've invented a whole story,
and you're twisting everything to fit.
No, I'm not.
Yu Seongwon
has been killing people continuously.
You're out of your mind. [exclaims]
Stay out of this investigation!
- Sir.
- Chief Park.
The body of Joo Hyera's junior officer
was delivered to her.
Can she stay on this case?
She can't.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Team 2!
Don't spin some story like she did.
Find the real killer, got it?
- Yes, sir.
Damn it.
[door closes]
[♪ music fades]
Leave the country right now.
I told you I have an exhibition.
Must I really go through this
because of you?
[inhales sharply]
I think we'll have to kill
that boyfriend of yours.
- What?
- Why?
Do you love him?
[scoffs]
You don't know anything about that.
[sighs heavily]
You had me because you wanted
to be the chairman's second wife.
But
even just a little,
did you ever love me?
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[breathes deeply]
Isoo told me
that I ended up broken because of you.
So you should take responsibility.
Leave the country for a while.
The police have nothing on me.
They don't have any evidence.
Stay away until things settle down!
[swears softly]
Should I just come clean?
Seeing you with your head down
and your hands cuffed,
being dragged around,
while reporters take pictures of you...
[laughing] ...might actually be quite fun.
- Honestly.
- [♪ music fades]
What do you mean
Yu Seongwon has been killing people?
Are you saying he's a serial killer?
Yes.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Two of Yu Seongwon's models
and his underclassman are missing.
Detective Joo thinks
Yu Seongwon was inspired by his murders
and created these pieces.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
After Kim Heejun went missing,
Yu Seongwon left for the UK.
He came back recently for an exhibition.
Detective Joo moved back here
to catch Yu Seongwon.
To catch Yu Seongwon?
Then what happened to Jeong Minjae?
He was following Yu Seongwon,
and then we lost contact with him.
[sighs deeply]
Do you think
Yu Seongwon is the killer, too?
Yes, I'm certain.
He killed Younghwan to provoke me.
But we don't have any evidence.
[♪ music fades]
These are old case files.
Let's check them
to see if we've missed anything.
- Okay.
- [sighs]
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
[sighs in exasperation]
[sniffles, sighs heavily]
[breath trembling, sighing]
Hyera.
[Hyera sniffles, sighs]
[exhales softly]
I know how you feel.
[breath trembling]
[Changun]
Just pull yourself together first.
We're going to catch Yu Seongwon.
It may seem hopeless right now,
but we'll catch him in the end.
[breath continues trembling]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gripping, ominous music playing]
[Isoo] You didn't have a mother like that.
That's why you ended up completely broken.
You were damaged beyond repair.
Did you feel scared and run to your mom?
Did you beg her for help?
From the mom who despises you?
[sighs softly]
[scoffs]
[sighs wearily]
[sighs deeply]
[shattering]
[breathing heavily]
[clangs]
[hurried footsteps approaching]
[sighs softly]
[groans softly]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales deeply]
[♪ music swells]
[sighs softly]
[♪ music fades]
TWO DAYS EARLIER
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
[scoffs]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
- [taser crackling]
- [heavy thud]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[♪ ominous chord swells]
[chuckles softly]
[♪ melancholy piano music playing]
[Mr. Hwang grunts]
[flames roaring]
[♪ music swells]
[inhales sharply]
[exhales deeply]
[chuckles softly]
[laughs maliciously]
[♪ music fades]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 12
THE MADNESS IS FINALLY UNVEILED
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
What's Yu Seongwon's weakness?
Don't touch my son.
[Taegyun] You're suspended as of now.
[Isoo] I'll resign.
[Hyera] Jin Isoo!
[Isoo] Detective Joo,
stay and hold the line.
Hello! Watch how far I can go.
They're even threatening to sue.
I have a plane ready. Get out now.
Yu Seongwon's flying out in two hours.
Just go and arrest him first.
Now's the time to repay your debt.
- [tires screech]
- [Kyungjin] Pull over!
[man] Jin Isoo is in the studio.
Burn them all.
[Seongwon] Do you really think
you can catch me?
[♪ music fades]
[woman] Mr. Yu, welcome.
Hello.
Looking handsome as always.
How have you been?
Doing well. How about you, Director?
It's been frantic getting ready
for the exhibition.
This way, please.
I have the pieces all set up.
What do you think?
[♪ gripping, ominous music playing]
As for this exhibition...
That one is the centerpiece.
It should be the first thing people see
when they walk in.
It needs to feel real...
as if it were alive.
Understood?
Translated by Hyesoo Lee